[Music]
hi everyone I really don't know about
this one life insurance it was
introduced to me by my husband since his
captain in the same vessel was also our
client of sunlight and told him its
benefits and importance
my husband was encouraged to get it for
us and I immediately agree to since it
would be best to get an insurance
especially nowadays that we experience
pandemic jutsu appropiate 19 fortunately
I knew our financial adviser mrs. Riggs
and grace Escoffier Delphine true
captain Delphine since she was his wife
at first I was hesitant to talk since I
really don't know her but her loosing
personality and very accommodating it
made me feel at least she patiently
answers all my queries and made me feel
secure when we will get a plan I get my
first financial plan last May 20 2020
intended for my kids and for my
retirement since I'm not working anymore
and I just manage a business which and
internet to pay instead our financial
adviser explains to me everything
through online video chat up and
processing it made me feel hassle free
since it is all done through online
application so that's why I decided to
avail the San Max a link Prime vol
because it is not a traditional life
insurance policy
in this plan the premium provides a life
insurance while being invested to an
investment one aside from that it has
also a fun value that you can withdraw
to meet your financial goals while
living I also have a pending application
for my kids of guaranteed product named
San a smarter life belief for in you get
life insurance coverage and a lifetime
guaranteed cash benefits that I think
fits perfectly for my children for their
future needs so what are you waiting for
I definitely encourage you to get a son
life insurance plan if you want to have
a peace of mind knowing that the future
of your family is secured
especially today that we are in a great
crisis and with the help of our
financial advisers who really keeps in
touch to explain till the end so no need
to worry anymore
thank you sunlight
[Applause]